{
    "subject": "resource/Leipzig",
    "predicate": "property/areaCode",
    "object": "341",
    "human_readable": "The area code of Leipzig is 341.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8454370498657227,
            "question": "What is the area code for Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8376766443252563,
            "question": "Which area code corresponds to Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8176233768463135,
            "question": "What area code is used for Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7314481735229492,
            "question": "Which German city has an area code of 341?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5825486779212952,
            "question": "If you were calling someone in Leipzig, what area code would you dial?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5822305679321289,
            "question": "What is the designated code for telephone numbers in Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3215221166610718,
            "question": "To call someone in Leipzig, what digits would you use before their number?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27793261408805847,
            "question": "What number do you need to add when making a call to Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25747150182724,
            "question": "What numerical prefix identifies calls made to Leipzig?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2560431957244873,
            "question": "What three-digit number precedes a Leipzig phone number?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The area code of Leipzig is 341.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6524_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What numerical prefix identifies calls made to Leipzig?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6524_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What number do you need to add when making a call to Leipzig?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6524_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To call someone in Leipzig, what digits would you use before their number?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6524_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6524_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that the area code for Leipzig, Germany is 341, which directly supports the statement \"The area code of Leipzig is 341.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}